{
    "id": "df5e1f1dc2974be1b3cf2f28af31f35c",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We commenced work ………………… Monday.",
            "description": "From indicates some point of time. It is used with all tenses.",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "in",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He sat …………………….. a chair.",
            "description": "We use on to speak of things at rest.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "onto"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I slept ……………………… 11 o’clock.",
            "description": "We use till to indicate time. We use up to to indicate distance or quantity.",
            "answers": [
                "till",
                "until",
                "up to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I have not eaten anything ……………………… yesterday.",
            "description": "Since denotes some point of time in the past. It is used with a perfect tense.",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We walked …………………………. the end of the street.",
            "description": "We use up to to talk about distance.",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "till",
                "up to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "An old feud existed ………………………. the two families.",
            "description": "We use between to speak of two people or things.",
            "answers": [
                "between",
                "among",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The caravan must reach its destination …………………………… sunset.",
            "description": "We use before to indicate time we use in front of to indicate position.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "before",
                "in front of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I will return ……………………….. an hour.",
            "description": "We use in before a noun denoting a period of time",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "by",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I must start …………………….. dawn.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I have been waiting for this moment …………………….. years.",
            "description": "We use for to indicate duration.",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "from",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He is …………………… the top of the class.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "That is the boy I was speaking ……………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "of",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}